Crack: Cocaine, Corruption & Conspiracy is a
documentary film directed by Stanley Nelson.
A cheap, powerful drug emerges during a recession,
igniting a moral panic fueled by racism.
Explore the complex history of crack in the 1980s.
Self – Neuroscientist, played by Carl Hart.
Self, played by Koe Rodriguez.
Self, played by Nelson George.
Self, played by Corey Pegues.
Self, played by Samson Styles.
Self, played by Felipe Luciano.
Crack: Cocaine, Corruption & Conspiracy is a 2021 American documentary
film made for Netflix and directed by Stanley Nelson.
Its story focuses on the emergence and effects of the 1980s crack epidemic in the United
States, which resulted in negative effects on America's inner cities.
The film was released on January 11, 2021.
The film explores themes of drug smuggling, drug
addiction, cocaine, drug scene, crack.
The tone is thought_provoking.